[Waco] Sanger-Heights Neighborhood Term Paper and Research collection, Inclusive: 1986-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Properties, 1985-1996, undated; 1
  - 2801 Sanger Ave, Paige Ingram (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 2814 Sanger Ave, Michael Giles, 1994 December (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 2823 Sanger Ave, James Lyden Hudec (1 of 2), 1994 November (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 2824 Sanger Ave, Monica Cummings (1 of 2), 1994 December (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 2824 Sanger Ave, Monica Cummings (2 of 2), 1994 December (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 2901 Sanger Ave, Jim Miller (1 of 2), 1995 May (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2909 Sanger Ave, Rosalie E. Simons (1 of 2), 1992 May (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 2909 Sanger Ave, Rosalie E. Simons (2 of 2), 1992 May (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 2910 Sanger Ave, Katherine Sherman, 1995 May (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 2915 Sanger Ave, Kathy Payne, 1989 December (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 1415 Washington Ave, Allison J. Hall (1 of 2), 1992 May (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - 1415 Washington Ave, Allison J. Hall (2 of 2), 1992 May (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 1505 Washington Ave, Jill Knudson (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Audiocassettes, 1985-1996, undated; 2
  The Cassettes series, dated 1986-1995, includes oral interviews with home and business owners of properties in the Sanger Heights Neighborhood. Cassettes correspond to addresses in the Properties series. The series is arranged by street address and in good condition.
  Cassette tape
  - 811 N 4th Street, Ray V. Sardessai (2 of 2), 1994 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 1302 N. 13th Street, Anastasia Nenadyshina (3 of 3), 1994 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 514 N. 16th Street, Karen Caldbeck (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 624 N. 16th Street, Pamela R. Reynolds (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - 726 N. 16th Street, Katherine D. Lilly (2 of 2), 1989 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 920 N. 16th Street, Tanya Owen (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 521 N. 18th Street, Evan Hunter (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - 910 N. 18th Street, Wendi Parker (3 of 3), 1990 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 1105 N. 18th Street, Kenneth R. Bates (2 of 2), 1989 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 1226 N. 18th Street, Joannah Evans (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 934 N. 19th Street, Tracey Goodwin (2 of 4), 1989 April (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 934 N. 19th Street, Tracey Goodwin (3 of 4), 1989 April (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 934 N. 19th Street, Tracey Goodwin (4 of 4), 1989 April (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 511 N. 22nd Street, William Walter Edgard (3 of 3), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 521 N. 22nd Street, Jessamyn Allen (4 of 4), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 912 N. 22nd Street, Clare Satterfield (3 of 3), 1989 April (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - 921 N. 22nd Street, Lesley O’Connor (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 925 N. 22nd Street, Caroline Percy (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 1020 N. 22nd Street, Scott Fligor (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - 1312 N. 22nd Street, Stephanie Sagebiel (2 of 2), 1990 April (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 523 N. 23rd Street, Lori Rankin (3 of 3), 1988 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 915 N. 23rd Street, Cathy Stamey (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - 928 N. 23rd Street, Kurt Keller (2 of 2), 1988 April (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 118 N. 30th Street, Pamela A. Fierbach (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - 1328 & 1328 ½ S. 3rd Street, Susan Bell (2 of 2), 1994 July (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 1906 Austin Ave, Kendra Kubiak (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - 1906 Austin Ave, Kendra Kubiak (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - 1919 Bosque Blvd., Brett L. Bowden (3 of 4), 1988 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - 1919 Bosque Blvd., Brett L. Bowden (4 of 4), 1988 December (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - 2129 Bosque Blvd., (2 of 2), 1992 May (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - 2201 Bosque Blvd., Sanja Dimitrijevich (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 2201 Bosque Blvd., Sanja Dimitrijevich (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 2300 Bosque Blvd, Paige Reid (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - 3626 Castle Ave, Matt Clark (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - 3411 Chateau Ave, Caroline Kohl (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - 3501 Chateau Ave, Nikki Wisely (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 3525 Chateau Ave, Misty Redfield (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 1900 Colcord Ave, Paige K. Bardo (2 of 4), 1990 May (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 1900 Colcord Ave, Paige K. Bardo (3 of 4), 1990 May (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 1900 Colcord Ave, Paige K. Bardo (4 of 4), 1990 May (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 1901 Colcord Ave, Lucy Parks (2 of 4), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - 1901 Colcord Ave, Lucy Parks (3 of 4), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - 1901 Colcord Ave, Lucy Parks (4 of 4), 1992 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 2128 Colcord Ave, Chris Withrow & Beth McCleary (2 of 3), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - 2128 Colcord Ave, Chris Withrow & Beth McCleary (3 of 3), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 2200 Colcord Ave, Chrisanna Simpson (3 of 4), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 2200 Colcord Ave, Chrisanna Simpson (4 of 4), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - 2201 Colcord Ave, Lori Evans (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - 2223 Colcord Ave, Kraig Milton (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - 2315 Colcord Ave, Angela Richey (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 2316 Colcord Ave, Erin O’Brien (2 of 2), 1986 April (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - 2615 Colcord Ave, Sarah Jones (2 of 2), 1989 April (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - 2412 Colcord Ave, Tom Whitt (4 of 4), 1986 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - 1815 Colonial Ave, Carrie A. Platt (2 of 2), 1992 May (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - 1825 Colonial Ave, Mary Thompson (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - 1825 Colonial Ave, Mary Thompson (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 2301 Colonial Ave, Amy Beckwith (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - 2015 Ethel Ave, Steve Graves (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - 2211 Ethel Ave, Hao V. Vuong (2 of 2), 1987 April (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - 2223 — 2225 Ethel Ave, Alexander Chan (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 2403 Ethel Ave, Shannon L. Potts (2 of 5), 1990 May (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - 2403 Ethel Ave, Shannon L. Potts (3 of 5), 1990 May (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 2403 Ethel Ave, Shannon L. Potts (4 of 5), 1990 May (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 2403 Ethel Ave, Shannon L. Potts (5 of 5), 1990 May (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 2901 Fort Ave, Reagan Hughes (2 of 2), 1994 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 2216 Gorman Ave, Sandra L. Keyes (2 of 2), 1987 December (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 2220 Gorman Ave, Joseph J. Pothanikat (3 of 3), 1987 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 2226 Gorman Ave, Sharon Stacha (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - 2301 Gorman Ave, Brent Schotheis (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 2314 Gorman Ave, Michael Stevens (2 of 2), 1987 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - 2316 Gorman Ave, Holly Faulhaber (3 of 3), 1986 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 3818 Herwol Ave, Mindi Hardison (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - 3825 Herwol Ave, Courtney MacNaught (2 of 2), 1995 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - 2121 Homan Ave, Cheli Smith (2 of 2), 1989 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - 2121 Homan Ave, Rachel E. Wolfe (2 of 2)., 1987 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - 2411 Homan Ave, Timothy Weeks (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave, Kristen Malacarne (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave, Millie Nelson (2 of 2), 1990 May (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (4 of 6), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (5 of 6), 1992 December (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (6 of 6), 1992 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Christopher T. Forsythe (3 of 5), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Christopher T. Forsythe (4 of 5), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Christopher T. Forsythe (5 of 5), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 1712 Morrow Ave, Chris Reynolds (2 of 2), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 1801 Morrow Ave, Melisa Reeves (2 of 2), 1986 April (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 1815 Morrow Ave, Verena Albrand (2 of 2), 1990 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 1819 Morrow Ave, JoRhea Nagel (2 of 2), 1990 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - 2116 Morrow Ave, Lori Ann Lindsay (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - 2225 Morrow Ave, Andrea J. Weis (3 of 3), 1986 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 2820 Morrow Ave, Todd Rexrode (2 of 3), 1990 may (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - 2820 Morrow Ave, Todd Rexrode (3 of 3), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - 3300 Morrow Ave, Shannon Dixon (2 of 2), 1990 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 2200 Parrott Ave, Susan Rebecca Harvey (2 of 3), 1988 May (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - 2200 Parrott Ave, Susan Rebecca Harvey (3 of 3), 1988 May (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 2320 Parrott Ave, Christopher Bart Barber (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - 2326 Parrott Ave, Rhonda Crouch (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 2420 Parrott Ave, Sheryl Stewart (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - 2518 Parrott Ave, Michael Jakowitsch (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - 1914 Sanger Ave, Ji Young Kim (3 of 3), 1992 December (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - 1915 Sanger Ave, Shawn R. Stepp (2 of 2), 1988 November (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - 2715 Sanger Ave, Matt Rowan (2 of 2), 1944 December (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 2801 Sanger Ave, Paige Ingram (2 of 2), undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - 2823 Sanger Ave, James Lyden Hudec (2 of 3), 1994 November (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 2823 Sanger Ave, James Lyden Hudec (3 of 3), 1994 November (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - 2901 Sanger Ave, Jim Miller (2 of 2), 1995 May (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 1505 Washington Ave, Jill Knudson (2 of 2), 1992 December (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 3)